Guide to the AFSCME, Local 420, Hospital Workers Photographs PHOTOS.212
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Black and White Prints
  - Subseries C: Local 420
    - Sub-subseries iv: Demonstrations and Rallies
      - No Medicaid Cuts Campaign, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
      - No Privatization Campaigns, undated (Box 3, Folder 119)
      - [Parades], undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
      - Preparation For a Massive Demonstration, undated (Box 3, Folder 121)
      - Protest in First Union Baptist Church, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
      - [Protest/Rally at the Capitol Building in Albany], undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
      - Racial Harmony Campaign, undated (Box 3, Folder 124)
      - [Rally at a Church in Anniston, Alabama], undated (Box 3, Folder 125)
      - Rally at City Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 126)
      - [Rally at City Hall Park], undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
      - [Rally for South Africa], undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
      - Safe Elevators, undated (Box 3, Folder 129)
      - Save New York Hospital Campaign (flyers, drawings), undated (Box 3, Folder 130)
      - Stop Police Brutality -- [Justice for] Diallo [Rally], undated (Box 3, Folder 131)
      - [undated Demonstrations and Rallies--folder 1 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 132)
      - [undated Demonstrations and Rallies--folder 2 of 2] (Box 3, Folder 133)
      - Universal Healthcare Rally & Medicaid Cuts Rally, undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Sub-subseries v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists Robert Wilson Leadership Award, Aug 1983 (Box 3, Folder 135)
      - International Labor Communication Association Award [to Photographer Marshall McCullen. Probably 1984. See also folder #s 266 & 619.] (Box 3, Folder 136)
      - Lawrence Woffard/Voter Support at S.S. Meeting, Jan 22, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 137)
      - Black and White together [for] Economic Justice Campaign [Probably 1988] (Box 3, Folder 138)
      - Handling of Infectious Waste in Hospitals [Meeting], Sep 23, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 139)
      - Black History Month Salute to Nelson Mandela, Feb 15, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 140)
      - Central Office Employee Service Award Program, Jun 11, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 141)
      - National Health Care [Conference], Aug 31, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 142)
      - Chief Medical Examiner Office Work Safety Press Conference, Nov 10, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 143)
      - Black History [Month Proclamation New York] City Council, Feb 15, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 144)
      - [African American Day Parade. Probably 1996.] (Box 3, Folder 145)
      - WEP ["Workfare"] Workers [Press Conference? On the Steps of City Hall?; Meeting Same Day?] [See Folder # 762 for some matching negatives.], Oct 7, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 146)
      - Turkey Day, Nov 25, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 147)
      - [Meeting to Organize WEP "Workfare" Workers. Probably 1997.]] (Box 3, Folder 148)
      - [Award Presentation Ceremony with Mother Annie Williams], Feb 26, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 149)
      - [Meeting to Organize] WEP ["Workfare"] Workers, Jun 2, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 150)
      - Turkey Day, Nov 18, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 151)
      - [Award Presentation Ceremony & Christmas Party?], Dec 19, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 152)
      - [Tribute to] Reverend Councilman Wendell Foster, Feb 8, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 153)
      - Albany Weekend Black and P[uerto] R[ican] [Convention], Feb 14, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 154)
      - Black and Puerto Rican Weekend [Convention], Feb 12, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 155)
      - [Memorial Tribute? to] James Farmer [at City Hall?], Jul 21, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 156)
      - Turkey Day 420 NBC USA, Nov 17, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 157)
      - Turkey Day, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 158)
      - [Memorial Services for Patrick Dorismond], Mar 29, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 159)
      - DC 2292 (4-4-??), DC 2034 (1-18-??), DC 1999 (1-20) [Meetings; April 4, year unknown], undated (Box 4, Folder 160)
      - [A Funeral], undated (Box 4, Folder 161)
      - [Boycott Greyhound for Union Busting Meeting/Rally], undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
      - City of N.Y. Proclamation, undated (Box 4, Folder 163)
      - Daily News Stop Union Busting Breakfast, undated (Box 4, Folder 164)
      - [Health Care for All New York Campaign/Petition], undated (Box 4, Folder 165)
      - Martin Luther King Jr. High School [Voices of 420 Concert], undated (Box 4, Folder 166)
      - National Health Insurance Now Campaign, undated (Box 4, Folder 167)
      - Press Conferences, undated (Box 4, Folder 168)
      - Regional Institute for Union Women [Meeting] July 30-Aug 4, undated (Box 4, Folder 169)
      - [Turkey Day -- Preacher], undated (Box 4, Folder 170)
      - [Turkey Day -- undated] (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Sub-series v: Events, Sub-sub-subseries b: Charity
      - WLIB (Radio Station) African Relief [Broadcast], Nov 1984 (Box 4, Folder 172)
      - Voices of 420 "Jamaican Relief Concert" Memorial Baptist Church, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 173)
      - Hurricane [Hugo] Victim Support [Probably 1989] (Box 4, Folder 174)
      - [Voices of 420 Concert in Support of Victims of Hurricane Andrew. Probably 1992. ] (Box 4, Folder 175)
      - Mother Hale/Hale House Fundraiser, Aug 25, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 176)
      - [Voices of 420 Concert to Support Hurricane Hortense Victims. Probably 1996.] (Box 4, Folder 177)
      - Water for Puerto Rico [Hurricane Relief], Oct 9, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 178)
      - [Concert and Fundraiser for the Victims of Hurricane Georges], Oct 9, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 179)
      - Concert for Flood Victims North Carolina, Nov 10, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 180)
      - Rocky Mount, North Carolina Food, Nov 12, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 181)
      - [Charity -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Hearings
      - Health and Hospitals Corporation [Hearing], Nov 8, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 183)
      - City Council Hearing in Harlem [on Harlem Hospital], Apr 15, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 184)
      - City Council Health Committee Hearing, Mar 12, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 185)
      - State Hearing Health and Hospitals Corporation, Oct 1, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 186)
      - Hearing with Stanley Hill & James Butler, undated (Box 4, Folder 187)
      - [Hearings -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Sub-subseries vii: International Friendship/Solidarity
      - [Local 420 Delegation Visit to] National Workers Union of Jamaica, Jan 23, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 189)
      - Bermuda Industrial Union Labor Day, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 190)
      - [Antigua Workers Union, 32nd Annual Delegates Conference], 1998 (Box 4, Folder 191)
      - Antigua [Workers Union, 33rd Annual Delegates Conference], Sep 19, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 192)
      - [Bermuda Industrial Union Banquet], undated (Box 4, Folder 193)
      - [Free Mandela Demonstration], undated (Box 4, Folder 194)
      - [Trip to Jerusalem, Israel. 1970s?], undated (Box 4, Folder 195)
      - [Visitors from unions from overseas?], undated (Box 4, Folder 196)
      - [Welcome Nelson Mandela], undated (Box 4, Folder 197)
      - [Welcome Sister Khumbu Mtinanza of South Africa], undated (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Local Officers
      - Brown, Dorothy (Retirement & Other Pics), Jul 1983 (Box 4, Folder 199)
      - [Butler, James accepting "Outstanding Union Leadership Award"], Feb 22, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 200)
      - Butler, James -- B[irth]day Celebration [Probably 1984] (Box 4, Folder 201)
      - [Butler, James' 20th Anniversary Celebration], Oct 9, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 202)
      - Butler, James and Friends, Sep 8, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 203)
      - [Butler, James Speaking at Black History Month Meeting at DC37 Local 375], Feb 16, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 204)
      - Butler, James 25 Years Anniversary, Oct 11, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 205)
      - [Butler, James] -- Black Executive Award, Jan 22, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 206)
      - Butler, James -- [Awarded the Coaltion of Black Trade Unionists] Award, Aug 19, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 207)
      - Butler, James [accepting award from] Assemblyman Nick Perry, Oct 15, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 208)
      - Butler, James Honored, Jul 21, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 209)
      - Butler, James & Alejandro Ruiz (president & vice president), undated (Box 5, Folder 210)
      - Butler, James Awarded a Black Leather Case, undated (Box 5, Folder 211)
      - [Butler, James Presented Award by the Grace Congregational Church of Harlem], undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
      - Butler, James and Choir [at] Church, undated (Box 5, Folder 213)
      - Butler, James -- Dinner & Awards, undated (Box 5, Folder 214)
      - Butler, James & Louis Albano, undated (Box 5, Folder 215)
      - [Butler, James Meets with Various 420 Units], undated (Box 5, Folder 216)
      - Butler, James and Sarah Kennedy Honored by Morris Brown College, undated (Box 5, Folder 217)
      - Butler, James Speaks, undated (Box 5, Folder 218)
      - Butler, James -- Swearing in [Local Officers?], undated (Box 5, Folder 219)
      - [Butler, James -- Group Photographs undated] (Box 5, Folder 220)
      - [Butler, James -- Portraits undated] (Box 5, Folder 221)
      - Butler, James with City Hospital Employees, undated (Box 5, Folder 222)
      - Chapman, Freida at International Labor Press Association's Convention (Florida) [See Folder # 764 for some matching negatives.], 1983 (Box 5, Folder 223)
      - Election ([for] Officers), 1981 (Box 5, Folder 224)
      - Executive Board/Shop & Shop Steward Conference, Aug 1, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 225)
      - Jove, Mary Retirement, Oct 1987 (Box 5, Folder 226)
      - Kennedy, Sarah, undated (Box 5, Folder 227)
      - [Local 420 Officers -- General], undated (Box 5, Folder 228)
      - Ruiz, Alejandro (vice president), undated (Box 5, Folder 229)
      - [Smith], Ken[dreth] [at?] Goldwater [Hospital?], undated (Box 5, Folder 230)
      - Webb, James, undated (Box 5, Folder 231)
      - Webb, James -- Retirement Party, undated (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Sub-subseries ix: Meetings
      - [Executive Board Meeting -- at Seawind Beach Resort -- Montego Bay, Jamaica], Jun 11, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 233)
      - Conference, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 234)
      - Housekeeping Aide Meeting, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 235)
      - Citywide Nurses Aides, Mar 3, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 236)
      - [Meeting (in Preparation for?) March for Jobs, Justice & Racial Harmony. Probably 4/4/1993.], Apr 4, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 237)
      - Breakfast Meeting, Feb 9, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 238)
      - PCT Meeting, Feb 18, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 239)
      - Harlem [Hospital? Meeting], May 28, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 240)
      - Town Hall Meeting Health Care Sen[ator] Paterson, Feb 17, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 241)
      - [A Local 420 Meeting], undated (Box 5, Folder 242)
      - [A Meeting and Swearing In], undated (Box 5, Folder 243)
      - ["AFSCME Council 79" Meeting], undated (Box 5, Folder 244)
      - [Conference (Steven Van Zandt Present)], undated (Box 5, Folder 245)
      - Contract Meeting, undated (Box 5, Folder 246)
      - Convention at the Fairmont Hotel, undated (Box 5, Folder 247)
      - Delegate Convention, undated (Box 5, Folder 248)
      - Delegate Dinner, undated (Box 5, Folder 249)
      - Delegate Meeting pt 1, undated (Box 5, Folder 250)
      - Delegate Meeting pt 2, undated (Box 5, Folder 251)
      - [Early (ca. 1970s, early 1980s) Meetings -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 5, Folder 252)
      - Local 420 Convention, undated (Box 6, Folder 253)
      - [Meeting at the International Inn, Washington D.C. "Democratic Agenda" & (separate shoot) Meeting in a Church], undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
      - Meeting in Church, undated (Box 6, Folder 255)
      - Meeting with [Reverend Al] Sharpton in a Church, undated (Box 6, Folder 256)
      - [Miscellaneous 420 Meetings -- Dates Unknown -- folder 1 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 257)
      - [Miscellaneous 420 Meetings -- Dates Unknown -- folder 2 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 258)
      - [Miscellaneous 420 Meetings -- Dates Unknown -- folder 3 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
      - [Miscellaneous 420 Meetings -- Dates Unknown -- folder 4 of 4], undated (Box 6, Folder 260)
      - Shortage of Staff & Job Freeze, undated (Box 6, Folder 261)
      - Union Members (Delegates) Small Table Meetings, undated (Box 6, Folder 262)
      - Union Officials Meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Sub-subseries x: Personalities
      - [Barondess, Jeremiah], undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
      - Mother Annie Williams (including her funeral in May 2000), undated (Box 6, Folder 265)
      - Photographer [Marshall McCullen. See also folder: Int'l Labor Communication Association Award. See also folder #s 136 & 619.], undated (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Sub-subseries xi: Political
      - Voter Drive/Conference of Black Leaders, Apr 29, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 267)
      - [Vote Mondale/Ferraro. Probably 1984.] (Box 6, Folder 268)
      - [NCIPA Black Belt Defense Committee Benefit Luncheon], Jan 23, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 269)
      - Dukakis Campaign, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 270)
      - [Rally for Michael Dukakis in Memorial Baptist Church? and at Harlem Hospital], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 271)
      - Jesse Jackson [For President], 1988 (Box 6, Folder 272)
      - Voices of 420 "Jesse Jackson for Pres." Memorial Bapt. Church, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 273)
      - Voices of 420 St. Johns Bapt. [Church] Jesse Jackson for President, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 274)
      - Leonora Fulani Town Hall on Health Care [New Alliance Party], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 275)
      - [Town Hall on International Health Care -- Congressman Floyd Flake], 1992 (Box 6, Folder 276)
      - Clinton/Gore Phone Bank, Nov 3, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 277)
      - Endorses Adam Powell/ Endorses Colin Moore, Aug 30, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 278)
      - [Sharpton for US Senate], 1994 (Box 6, Folder 279)
      - [Edwin Edwards Campaign for Governor. Probably 1996.] (Box 6, Folder 280)
      - Phone Bank Election Day, Nov 15, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 281)
      - Rev. Sharpton for Mayor, Jan 20, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 282)
      - Rev. Al Sharpton for Mayor Kings County Hospital, Apr 4, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 283)
      - Ruth [Messinger] for Mayor -- Harlem Hospital, Oct 9, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 284)
      - Ruth [Messinger] for Mayor -- City Hall, Oct 24, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 285)
      - City Hall Bor. Pres. C. Virginia Fields, Jan 1, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 286)
      - Endorses Hon. Gregory Meeks, Jan 22, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 287)
      - Charlie King for Lt. Governor -- Harlem Hospital, Jul 1, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 288)
      - 420 for P[eter] Vallone for Gov[ernor], Oct 8, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 289)
      - Count Every Vote Campaign (Florida, [George W.] Bush Election) [Probably 2000] (Box 6, Folder 290)
      - [A Meeting at City Hall?], undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
      - [Clinton, Hillary], undated (Box 7, Folder 292)
      - Cuomo, Mario, undated (Box 7, Folder 293)
      - Dinkins, David, undated (Box 7, Folder 294)
      - [Fields, Virginia], undated (Box 7, Folder 295)
      - [Flake, Floyd], undated (Box 7, Folder 296)
      - [Gore, Al], undated (Box 7, Folder 297)
      - Hayes, Charles Campaign, undated (Box 7, Folder 298)
      - [Local 420 Supports Judge Hansel McGee], undated (Box 7, Folder 299)
      - Locals Meeting at DC 37 with David Dinkins, undated (Box 7, Folder 300)
      - Marshall, Helen, undated (Box 7, Folder 301)
      - McCall,Cuomo, and Koch with Local 420, undated (Box 7, Folder 302)
      - [Messinger, Ruth], undated (Box 7, Folder 303)
      - [Political Gatherings -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 7, Folder 304)
      - [Politicians -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 7, Folder 305)
      - [Reelect State Senator Efrain Gonzalez Jr.], undated (Box 7, Folder 306)
      - Register to Vote Campaign [See Folder #765 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 7, Folder 307)
      - Stop David Duke, undated (Box 7, Folder 308)
      - Una Clark for City Council (Local 420 Endorses), undated (Box 7, Folder 309)
      - Vote Lucy Campaign, undated (Box 7, Folder 310)
      - [Voter Registration -- Miscellaneous ], undated (Box 7, Folder 311)
      - [Young, Andrew], undated (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries a: General
      - [Miscellaneous Graduations (Nurses Aides, Medical Surgical Technicians, etc.) -- Unidentified and undated] (Box 7, Folder 313)
      - Nurse Aides, undated (Box 7, Folder 314)
      - Nurses, undated (Box 7, Folder 315)
      - [Occupational Safety and Worksite Working Conditions], undated (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries b: Bellevue Hospital
      - Bellevue [Hospital?] Laundry Party, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 317)
      - Bellevue Hospital Press Conference On Congressional TB Bill, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 318)
      - Bellevue Hospital Visit from Budget Secretary, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 319)
      - Bellevue Hospital Graduation, Mar 15, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 320)
      - President Clinton's Budget Director Tour of Bellevue Hospital, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 321)
      - Bellevue Nurses Aide/Tech. Graduation, Mar 15, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 322)
      - Bellevue Hospital Rally, Sep 12, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 323)
      - Rally Bellevue [Hospital], Jun 4, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 324)
      - Bellevue [Hospital Rally], Oct 26, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 325)
      - Bellevue [Rally] 6/4 [year unknown], undated (Box 7, Folder 326)
      - [Bellevue Hospital Graduation], undated (Box 7, Folder 327)
      - [Bellevue Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 7, Folder 328)
      - [Rally at Bellevue Hospital -- "Bellevue is Not South Africa"], undated (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries c: Bronx Municipal Hospital
      - Press Conference at Bronx Municipal Hospital re: Injured Nurses Aide, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 330)
      - Bronx Municipal Nurses Aide Grad[uation], Dec 10, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 331)
      - [Bronx Municipal Hospital 35th Year Anniversary Celebration?], undated (Box 7, Folder 332)
      - [Bronx Municipal Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 7, Folder 333)
      - Bronx Municipal See the Light Bronx Urban League Awards Ceremony, undated (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries d: Brooklyn Central Laundry
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry (Employee Appreciation Day), Jun 18, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 335)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry (Needle), Jun 30, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 336)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Apr 5, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 337)
      - Save Brooklyn Central Laundry 1st Baptist Church, Jul 21, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 338)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Oct 28, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 339)
      - Night Rally Brooklyn Central Laundry, Mar 3, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 340)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Apr 27, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 341)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Jun 11, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 342)
      - Brooklyn Central Laundry [Rally], Oct 28, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 343)
      - [Brooklyn Central Laundry is Not for Sale Rally] [See Folder #768 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 7, Folder 344)
      - [Brooklyn Central Laundry -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 7, Folder 345)
      - [Save Brooklyn Central Laundry Rally], undated (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries e: Coler-Goldwater Hospital
      - Bird S. Coler [Hospital] -- Installation Dispute [Fall 1984] (Box 8, Folder 347)
      - Coler Graduation, Oct 31, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 348)
      - Coler Christmas Party for Children of Employees [Probably 12/1987], Dec 1987 (Box 8, Folder 349)
      - Goldwater Nurses Aide Graduation, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 350)
      - Goldwater Hospital Ribbon Ceremony Greenhouse, Aug 9, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 351)
      - Goldwater Memorial Hospital Graduation, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 352)
      - Goldwater Hospital Med Surg Tech Graduation, Jun 5, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 353)
      - [Goldwater Memorial Hospital Nurses Aides Graduation. Probably 12/1997.], Dec 1, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 354)
      - [Swearing in at] Coler Hospital, Apr 26, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 355)
      - Coler/Goldwater Hospital MST Graduation, Aug 1, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 356)
      - [Coler Memorial Hospital Demonstration], undated (Box 8, Folder 357)
      - [Coler-Goldwater Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 8, Folder 358)
      - Graduates of Goldwater Hospital from Nurses Aides to H.S.I.s, undated (Box 8, Folder 359)
      - Goldwater [Hospital] Nursing Aide Graduation, undated (Box 8, Folder 360)
      - [Coler-Goldwater Hospital Miscellaneous Graduations], undated (Box 8, Folder 361)
      - [Stop Racial Descrimination Rally at Coler-Goldwater], undated (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries f: Coney Island Hospital
      - Coney Island Protest, Sep 17, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 363)
      - Coney Island Hospital Community Meet[ing], Sep 20, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 364)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Community Meeting], Mar 9, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 365)
      - Coney Island Rally, Mar 9, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 366)
      - Coney Island [Hospital Rally] [See Folder #770 for some matching negatives.], Jul 1, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 367)
      - Coney Island Hospital Rally, Sep 24, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 368)
      - Coney Island 54 Meet[ing], Jan 21, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 369)
      - Coney Island 54 Rally, Jan 28, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 370)
      - Coney Island 54 City Hall, Feb 9, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 371)
      - Coney Island [Hospital] Night Rally 54, Feb 18, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 372)
      - Coney Island 54 [Rally], Feb 19, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 373)
      - [Coney Island Rally], Nov 6, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 374)
      - Coney Island [Rally] 2/19 [year unknown], undated (Box 8, Folder 375)
      - Coney Island [Rally] 4/19 [year unknown], undated (Box 8, Folder 376)
      - C[oney] I[sland] Church CI 54, undated (Box 8, Folder 377)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Graduation], undated (Box 8, Folder 378)
      - [Coney Island Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 8, Folder 379)
      - Coney Island [Rally] [See Folder #773 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 8, Folder 380)
      - Coney Island 54 [Rally], undated (Box 8, Folder 381)
      - Coney Island Rally (Burger King), undated (Box 8, Folder 382)
      - [Coney Island Rally (Burger King) -- Autumn], undated (Box 8, Folder 383)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Rally -- Stop Murdering Public Hospitals] [See Folder # 772 for some matching negatives.], undated (Box 8, Folder 384)
      - [Coney Island Hospital Victory Meeting], undated (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries g: Cumberland Hospital
      - Cumberland Hospital [Service Award Ceremony], May 13, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 386)
      - [Cumberland Hospital -- Miscellaneous], undated (Box 8, Folder 387)
      - Save Cumberland [Rally], undated (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Units, Sub-sub-subseries h: Elmhurst Hospital
      - Elmhurst [Hospital] Payday Protest, Sep 7, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 389)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital Meeting-probably 6/13/1990], Jun 13, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 390)
      - [National] Housekeeping [Week] (Elmhurst [Hospital]), Oct 1, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 391)
      - Elmhurst Opening of New Center, Nov 9, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 392)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital Antiprivatization Rally-1994 or later] (Box 8, Folder 393)
      - Mrs. Steele Retirement [Elmhurst Hospital], Nov 20, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 394)
      - [Elmhurst Hospital Meeting], 1997 (Box 8, Folder 395)
      - McDonald's OUT!!! [Rally] Elmhurst Hospital, Mar 5, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 396)
      - Elmhurst Hospital [Rally] No McDonald's, Apr 22, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 397)
      - Elmhurst Hospital [Rally] No McDonald's, May 19, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 398)
      - Elmhurst [Hospital] Rally [No McDonald's], Sep 25, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 399)
      - Elmhurst [Hospital] Rally [No McDonald's], Dec 24, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 400)
      - Elmhurst [Hospital] Rally [No McDonald's], Mar 5, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 401)